Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Beyond Redemption
Episode 23
Where would Cha Erlang keep the antidote?
Something so precious…
he wouldn’t carry it on him, would he?
Sorry.
Jay.
Wolffy, why are you so absent-minded?
Jay, if we accidentally get hit by the Boss’s miasma,
what should we do then?
I know.
You mean…
I’ve never been afflicted by it myself,
but a companion of ours once accidentally breathed in the miasma.
You could ask him about it.
That’s right—he would definitely know about the antidote.
Big Sister, are you alright?
You shouldn’t be walking around.
I trust Wolffy will bring the antidote soon.
I’m afraid I can’t wait that long.
I have another way; come with me.
To what do I owe the pleasure of this visit?
I see your face is drained of color and your eyes look listless.
It seems the rumors are true; you’ve been afflicted by a potent miasma.
Cut the chatter—how can this miasma be cured?
It can’t be cured.
What about this?
There is one method I could try.
Delicious century eggs, mysterious tears…
…and a smile full of joy.
But there is one ingredient in particular that is truly unique.
This is it.
A sandshark’s reverse scale.
A sandshark?
Isn’t that quite common?
It is, but as for the reverse scale…
Only the Golden Sandshark has it.
Can we trust what he says?
I have indeed heard before
that the Golden Sandshark’s reverse scale has miraculous properties.
But those sandsharks are incredibly ferocious.
And this time, it has to be the Golden one.
How about I give you two extra bottles of water?
I heard everything you said.
I can supply the other ingredients for you.
But you’ll have to get that reverse scale yourselves.
It’s too dangerous; I’m not going.
I’ll go right now.
Let’s go together.
Don’t worry, Big Sister; you still have us.
I need to hurry back and report to Boss.
Didn’t you get hit by the miasma a while back?
You should rest more if you’re not feeling well; I’ll help you with the work.
Thanks a lot, Wolffy.
But the miasma was cleared up ages ago.
How did you cure it?
Do you know where the antidote is?
Boss provides it.
You just have to go and queue up to get it yourself.
So, the antidote is just being handed out like that?
Yeah.
Boss is worried that one of our own might accidentally get exposed to the miasma again,
so he’s distributing the antidote now.
Talk about a stroke of luck.
Aren’t you helping me with my work?
Do your own work yourself.
Attention, everyone.
You cannot open your eyes for three days after taking the medicine.
Otherwise, you’ll go permanently blind.
There’s a catch like that?
Hurry and take this to Weslie.
Wolffy,
I need to talk to you.
But I’ve got other things to do.
Never mind, then.
Jay, come into the cockpit with me.
They’re going into the cockpit?
I might be able to see the map and find the rift.
Boss,
let me handle such a tough job.
You really are a model worker.
Go assemble those parts; we’ll need them later.
Didn’t you say we were going to the cockpit?
The utility room next to the cockpit counts as part of the cockpit, too.
How did it come to this?
We can’t get away now.
Is the Golden Sandshark right here?
Look, there are so many small sandsharks.
In what way are they small?
Do you see that glowing reverse scale on its body?
Big Sister.
You stay here and wait for us.
Be careful.
We can’t get the reverse scale if we keep getting dragged along by the sandshark like this.
We need to find a way to restrain it.
I’ve got an idea.
Oh no.
Fishy, I’m sorry.
There’s something glowing in its gills.
That’s a reverse scale. It’s like a bad tooth to it.
That’s why it’s so agitated.
We didn’t mean to disturb you.
Removing that reverse scale won’t be easy.
You’re injured now; let me take the reverse scale.
No, let’s do it together.
Alright.
Leave the sandsharks behind you to me.
Its back is too slippery.
Otherwise, I could have pulled them out with a line.
Brother Weslie!
Weslie.
It’s all set up.
But why is Boss setting up such a huge cage?
Don’t you know? This cage is for catching Blue Scarf and the others.
The Boss found out Blue Scarf was looking for a sandshark’s reverse scale to make an antidote.
He’s waiting for Blue Scarf and the sandshark to wear each other out in a fight.
Then we can swoop in and reap the rewards.
What?
Weslie must be with her right now.
I have to give them a hand.
I wonder if there’s any news from the people Boss sent out.
How did you suddenly wake up?
It got away.
They’ve all gone into hiding; we can’t find where they are at all.
Are you okay?
Brother Weslie, the sandshark is to your left.
To think you could spot the sandshark’s trail like that.
My eyesight is excellent; I’ll help you keep watch.
Watch out behind you, Big Sister.
Brother Weslie, it’s up ahead to your right.
Ahead.
Got it.
Right.
It’s the Golden Sandshark—watch out!
Got it.
Blue Scarf.
Cha Erlang.
Don’t be rash; let’s retreat for now.
Since you’re already here, there’s no need to rush off.
Rest assured, I’ll finish you off myself before the symptoms kick in.
Go retrieve the cage.
Boss.
Boss, if we don’t leave now,
the Sandshark is going to tear the vehicle apart.
Blue Scarf, we’ll settle our score another time.
Everyone, forget about the cage; let’s get out of here first.
Cha Erlang and the sandshark are both gone. Does that mean we’re safe?
Big Sister?
Are you okay?
I need to get you treated for the miasma quickly…but how do we break the cage open?
What is this?
Quick, open the cage.
Big Sister, hang in there.
Big Sister…Big Sister…
Did the earlier battle cause the miasma to spread?
Wolffy, hurry and bring the antidote over here.
It’s so cold.
Are you still cold?
Whenever I wasn’t feeling well, Mom used to hold me just like this.
It’s…you.
To be continued